BEW Gondola Pack 2 With Freight Animation Loads

A set of 7 Gondolas from the shapes found in the Ultimate Gondola Pack by "Funnelfan" Ted Curphey.

Step 1: Unpak the zip file which should give you 4 folders named ATSF_Gondolas  B&O_Gondolas
BNSF_Gondolas &  LeaseX_Gondolas      move these folders to your Trains/Trainset folder in MSTS.

the reason for seperating the wagons by road name is a: for those who have mini routes themed by 
railroad and b: to enable me in the future if i find other suitable wagons for the same road to 
have them added to the same themed folder later.

Step 2: create consists using  the MSTS Editor or whichever you prefer for doing the job, Enjoy

Credits:

Original Gondolas and textures: "Funnelfan" Ted Curphey.
Freight Animation shape files: David Rowie
Freight Animation Textures (except Coal, Lumber & Mixed Scrap Load): David Rowie
Freight Animation Lumber Textures: Steve Thompson
Freight Animation Mixed Scrap Load Textures: Jeff Auberpine
Freight Animation Coal Load:  Ian Macmillan
Gondola Photoskin Textures created by Bernard Grant and Jeff Auberpine
Photographs for all units by Jeff Auberpine
Truck textures to replace original FF-hardware:  JR-hardware Trucks by Jeff Auberpine

by Bernard Grant ( burgerbern )

